<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="consent_agreement">"We(Bhrigu Kansra, Ambika, Jatin Katyal) are a team of undergraduate machine learning enthusiasts and developers and as a part of Celestini Project India 2019, sponsored by Marconi Society and Google we are developing an Android based application to increase women safety by detecting sounds of Screams and Crying/Sobbing. For that we are crowdsourcing audio data samples of various individuals.


To make sure that we're able to share your data as part of a public data set with no privacy or other concerns, we need to get your agreement formally. If you would like to participate in providing some samples, please review and confirm your agreement to the following:
In agreement below, “us” or “we” refers to the team members of Celestini Project India 2019 that are Bhrigu Kansra, Ambika and Jatin Katyal.
1.	By participating, this application will ask for permission to use your microphone and prompt you to record(the “Study”) any of the 6 environmental context set . Each clip ideally should vary in length of 2 to 8 seconds( Generally 2 seconds for screams and 8 seconds for Outdoors and other context sets). Clips will only be sent to “us” when you press the ‘Upload’ button, or the ‘OK’ button on the dialog that appears once you’ve completed. At any point you can press the ‘Stop Recording’ button to pause the recording process.
2.	Your participation is voluntary and you may choose to cease participation at any time. You will not be compensated for your participation.
3.	By participating, you agree that “we” may use the clips to develop and improve its products, and share the clips with others, including the general public, for example, as part of a public dataset to facilitate research. You understand that your voice alone or in combination with other information could identify you. You specifically waive and release any potential intellectual property right, right of publicity, or right of privacy claim against “us” or others for use or sharing of your clips.
4.	Voice sample collected can be used for any scientific, non-commercial applications.
5.	WE MAKE NO WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO THE STUDY AND EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. IN NO EVENT WILL EITHER PARTY BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES UNDER THIS RELEASE IN MONETARY VALUE.
6.	This agreement does not create any agency or partnership relationship. This agreement is not assignable or transferable by you. This agreement is the parties’ entire agreement on this topic, superseding any prior or contemporaneous agreements. Any amendments must be in writing. Failure to enforce any of the provisions of this agreement will not constitute a waiver.
By clicking ‘I Agree’ you confirm that you are at least eighteen years of age, you understand the points above, and consent to the collection, use, and sharing of the Clips to “us”.

For queries, you can contact “us” at KINETICKANSRA@GMAIL.COM , AMBIKA.ARORA1998@GMAIL.COM , JK@CB.LK ."
</string>
    <string name="audio_description">"Sobb and Cry - audio contains noisy crying of females in an environment of distress.
     Scream - audio containing depicting screaming sounds instigated by a sudden distress induction.
     Outdoors - This includes amongst others, sounds due to vehicular traffic, when commuting in modes of transport like public buses, railways, cars, and auto rickshaws, and honking.
     Multimedia - This context includes artificial human sounds and music generated by televisions and radios. For example, sound samples from news and sports channels, comedy serials, and Indian serials are included.
     Human Gathering - This context includes sounds in situations where many people are together. A large number of people laughing, a crowd cheering, restaurants, malls, markets, seminars, applause by a crowd, and people talking loudly in a metro-rail, are a few examples.
     Conversations - This includes day to day life conversations."
    </string>
</resources>
